OrNET Browser
=============

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. We will not use or share your information with anyone. We have implemented a variety of procedures to protect your privacy when you are using our services.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible in our apps unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Overview:**

* No registration is required, to use our products and/or services.
* We do not request any personally identifiable information such as your e-mail address unless you will be contacting our support team.
* OrNET Browser do not store any record of people’s browsing history or log any personal information directly.
* We do not record your IP address. Third-party sites that you might be visiting using our Browser might do. For more, you can read the privacy policy for the third-party sites.
* Our VPN servers do not store any logs.
* We do not log URLs or any other information about websites that you might be visiting.
* We do not have access to your cookies or saved passwords.
* We do not have access to your downloaded files, favorite sites, preferences, or any bookmarked sites.

**Information Collection and Use**

None of your personal information is needed in order to download and use our software and/or services.

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your email address when you ask for help/support. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

**The app does not use third-party services that may collect information used to identify you. To ensure the true meaning of anonymity and complete protection of your privacy we don’t use any third-party services in our app.**

Personal information can be used in the following ways:

* To improve Services.
* To improve your User's experience.
* Feedback purposes.
* To statistically analyze user preference.
* To improve product development.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device's internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly.

### Security

We value your trust in providing us with your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. However, we have implemented a variety of procedures to protect your privacy when you are using our services.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our policy is not applicable to services offered by other companies and/or organizations and/or individuals, including products and/or sites that may be displayed through our browser or other sites linked to our services.

If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We’ll update this policy whenever we make material changes to our practices. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We hope you’ll find any changes agreeable, but if you’re not comfortable with changes to the info we collect or how we use it, we understand your choice to stop using our product.

This policy is effective as of **2024-25-12**

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://ornet.io/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).You can also contact us with your ideas about privacy and UI improvements.
